<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<type>database</type>
		<description>Language labels for grid elements</description>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="title">Accordion</label>
			<label index="description">Accordion container with arbitrary amount of pages.</label>
			<label index="option.singlePageMode">Single Page Mode: When checked, in accordion only one page can be opened at once.</label>
			<label index="option.collapsible">Collapsible: When checked, all pages of accordion can get closed again by clicking on header.</label>
			<label index="option.leaveAllItemsClosed">Leave all items closed: When enabled, all tiles of accordion are initially closed. Set focus of tiles is ignored.</label>
			<label index="option.heightStyle">Height Style: Controls the height of the accordion and each panel.</label>
			<label index="option.heightStyle.auto">Auto: All panels will be set to the height of the tallest panel.</label>
			<label index="option.heightStyle.fill">Fill: Expand to the available height based on the accordion's parent height.</label>
			<label index="option.heightStyle.content">Content: Each panel will be only as tall as its content.</label>
			<label index="option.on">On</label>
			<label index="option.off">Off</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="title">Akkordion</label>
			<label index="description">Akkordion-Container mit belieber Anzahl von Seiten.</label>
			<label index="option.singlePageMode">Einzel-Seiten-Modus: Wenn aktiv, wird im Akkordion immer nur eine Seite gleichzeitig geöffnet.</label>
			<label index="option.collapsible">Einklappbar: Wenn aktiv, können alle Seiten eines Akkordions wieder zusammengeklappt werden, wenn man erneut auf den Header klickt.</label>
			<label index="option.leaveAllItemsClosed">Alle Elemente geschlossen darstellen: Wenn aktiv, werden alle Seiten des Akkordion initial geschlossen dargestellt. Der gesetzte Fokus von Seiten wird dann ignoriert.</label>
			<label index="option.heightStyle">Höhenstil: Kontrolliert die Höhe des Akkordion und jeder Seite darin.</label>
			<label index="option.heightStyle.auto">Auto: Alle Seiten werden so hoch, die die höchste Seite.</label>
			<label index="option.heightStyle.fill">Füllen: Erweitert die Höhe aller Seiten, abhängig von der Höhe des Elternelements.</label>
			<label index="option.heightStyle.content">Inhalt: Jedes Seite wird so hoch, wie dessen Inhalt ist.</label>
			<label index="option.on">An</label>
			<label index="option.off">Aus</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>
